letterspro.com 2017-03-20

# Privacy - LettersPro.com

Your privacy is important to LettersPro.com. This privacy statement provides information about the personal information that LettersPro.com collects, and the ways in which LettersPro.com uses that personal information.

### Personal information collection

LettersPro.com may collect and use the following kinds of personal information:

  * information about your use of this website
  * information that you provide using for the purpose of registering with the website
  * information about transactions carried out over this website
  * information that you provide for the purpose of subscribing to the website services
  * any other information that you send to LettersPro.com

### Using personal information

LettersPro.com may use your personal information to:

  * administer this website
  * personalize the website for you
  * enable your access to and use of the website services
  * publish information about you on the website
  * send to you products that you purchase
  * supply to you services that you purchase
  * send to you statements and invoices
  * collect payments from you
  * send you marketing communications

Where LettersPro.com discloses your personal information to its agents or sub-contractors for these purposes, the agent or sub-contractor in question will be obligated to use that personal information in accordance with the terms of this privacy statement.

In addition to the disclosures reasonably necessary for the purposes identified elsewhere above, LettersPro.com may disclose your personal information to the extent that it is required to do so by law, in connection with any legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings, and in order to establish, exercise or defend its legal rights.

### Securing your data

LettersPro.com will take reasonable technical and organisational precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information.

LettersPro.com will store all the personal information you provide

Information relating to electronic transactions entered into via this website will be protected by encryption technology.

### Cross-border data transfers

Information that LettersPro.com collects may be stored and processed in and transferred between any of the countries in which LettersPro.com operates to enable the use of the information in accordance with this privacy policy.

In addition, personal information that you submit for publication on the website will be published on the internet and may be available around the world.

You agree to such cross-border transfers of personal information.

### Updating this statement

LettersPro.com may update this privacy policy by posting a new version on this website.

You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are familiar with any changes.

### Other websites

This website contains links to other websites.

LettersPro.com is not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of any third party.

### About cookies

This website uses cookies. By using this website and agreeing to this policy, you consent to LettersPro's use of cookies in accordance with the terms of this policy.

Cookies are files sent by web servers to web browsers, and stored by the web browsers.

The information is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server. This enables a web server to identify and track web browsers.

There are two main kinds of cookies: session cookies and persistent cookies. Session cookies are deleted from your computer when you close your browser, whereas persistent cookies remain stored on your computer until deleted, or until they reach their expiry date.

### Google cookies

LettersPro.com uses Google Analytics to analyse the use of this website. Google Analytics generates statistical and other information about website use by means of cookies, which are stored on users' computers. The information generated relating to our website is used to create reports about the use of the website. Google will store and use this information. Google's privacy policy is available at: http://www.google.com/privacypolicy.html.]

LettersPro.com publishes Google Adsense interest-based advertisements on this website. These are tailored by Google to reflect your interests. To determine your interests, Google will track your behaviour across the web using cookies. You can view, delete or add interest categories associated with your browser using Google's Ads Preference Manager, available at: http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/. You can opt-out of the Adsense partner network cookie at: http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html. However, this opt-out mechanism uses a cookie, and if you clear the cookies from your browser your opt-out will not be maintained. To ensure that an opt-out is maintained in respect of a particular browser, you should use the Google browser plug-in available at: http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/plugin.]

### Third party cookies

When you use this website, you may also be sent third party cookies.

### Refusing cookies

Most browsers allow you to refuse to accept cookies.

In Internet Explorer, you can refuse all cookies by clicking “Tools”, “Internet Options”, “Privacy”, and selecting “Block all cookies” using the sliding selector.

In Firefox, you can adjust your cookies settings by clicking “Tools”, “Options” and “Privacy”.

Blocking cookies will have a negative impact upon the usability of some websites.

### Credit

This document was created using a Contractology template available at http://www.freenetlaw.com.
